makingdifferent.com 2016-11-08

# Privacy Policy - Making Different

Every blogger looks forward for the privacy policy for its blog that manages the blog and collects, uses, maintains and discloses the information collected from the users, and in the makingdifferent.com privacy policy is applied to the site, the products and the services offered by my site that is makingdifferent.com. On this blog you will find many types of privacy policy like that of personal, Non-personal, web browser cookie, a collection of information and its protection, advertisement and much more. So lets have a look on each of the policy one by one by which you can share best experience with my amazing blog makingdifferent.com.

**Personal identification information**  
When users visit our site and register on the site, we may collect personal identification information from users in a variety of ways, and they get in contact with the activities, services, features and the resources that we make available on our site for our registered visitors. Users may be asked for few personal details like name, email address, mailing address, phone number etc., only if they wish to. Users can refuse to provide the personal information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain site related activities.

**Non-Personal identification information**  
Apart from the personal information we may also collect non-personal information about users whenever they interact or pass by our site. In this type of identification information it includes the browser name, type of computer, and the technical information about the users, i.e. the mean of connection with our site.

**How we use collected information**  
Makingdifferent collects and uses the information for the following purposes.

**To personalize the user experience**  
We may use the information to understand our users, how they use the services and resources provided by us on our site.  
**To improve our site for better experience**  
We keep on going through the information and the feedbacks that we receive from you, so that we can improve our site for the best experience of our visitors.

**To improve customer service**  
Your information helps us to respond to your customer service request and the support needs more effectively.

**To send periodic emails**  
The email ids provided by the users are used for providing the answers to their queries and questions asked by the users on our site.

**How we protect your information**  
Any of the user provide their information by a trust that we will secure and protect their information, Â so we adopt appropriate data collection, storage, and the security measures to protect unauthorized access, disclosure of your personal information, username, password and the data stored on our site.

**Sharing your personal information**  
We donâ€™t sell or trade any kind of personal information about our registered users with others, instead we may share generic aggregated demographic information, which is not linked to any personal identifying information regarding visitors and the users with our business partners and with any other officials.

**Advertising**  
Advertisements appearing on our site may be delivered to our users by the advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or the ones who uses your computer. This privacy policy doesnâ€™t cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Web browser cookies**  
Our site may use cookies to enhance the experience of the users. This policy places the cookies on their hard drive for record keeping purposes and sometimes to track the information about them. Users may also set their browser to refuse the use of cookies, or to alert you when the cookies are being sent, and if they do so note that some part of our site may fail to function properly or in its best way.

**Google Adsense**  
Some of the ads may be served by the google. Googles use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to the users based on their visit to our site. DART doesnâ€™t use any personal identification information about you.

**Changes to this privacy policy**  
In makingdifferent you can update any kind of the information provided by you at any time. And when we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our site. Thus we encourage the users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how are we helping to protect the personal information that we collect.

**Your acceptance**  
By using this site, you signify your acceptance of this policy.
